quepasa.com 2012-07-21

# Quepasa Privacy Policy

**Quepasa Privacy Policy**

Quepasa provides users of Quepasa.com and affiliated websites with access to a large collection of online resources including, but not limited to, content, news, search, email, chat, message boards, maps, personalized web pages, customization features and shopping services (referred to as "Service" or "Services").

Quepasa takes reasonable measures to respect the privacy of its users. This Privacy Policy covers your use, whether you register as a member or not, of Quepasa's Services. The information entered or posted through the Services may be available to be viewed or used by members of the public.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to Quepasa's Terms of Use and may be revised from time to time. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your initial or continued use of the Services constitutes your agreement with this Privacy Policy and any of its revisions.

**Children's Privacy**

Quepasa's Services are not intended for, nor directed to, persons under 14 years of age. Quepasa does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 14 years of age. If you are under 14 years of age, please do not use the Services. If Quepasa learns that personally identifiable information of a person under 14 years of age has been collected without verified parental consent, then Quepasa will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

Quepasa endeavors to help parents ensure that their children have a fun and safe online experience. Even though Quepasa is not directed towards children under the age of 14, we will permit parents to request a review of the information collected by Quepasa of their child's information by sending an email to [qpsupport@quepasacorp.com](mailto:qpsupport@quepasacorp.com). Quepasa may take steps to verify the identity of anyone requesting information about a child to ensure that this person is in fact the child's parent or legal guardian.

You may at any time decline to submit personally identifiable information in using the Service, in which case certain features and/or the Service may not be available to you. You may update or correct your profile information at any time by visiting the Profile webpage and associated tabs. We take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access to your profile. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and accuracy of your account information at all times.

**Information Collected**

Quepasa gathers information related to your use of the Service to better understand how our users, as a group, use the Service and the various features thereof, as well as to help us fit offerings to you as an individual and to conduct market research. Information may be used by Quepasa for commercial purposes, including advertising, targeted advertising, marketing, and promotional activities. You provide, and Quepasa collects, personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email, gender, age, and other information upon registration and throughout the use of the Service. Quepasa also collects web activity information such as navigational or technical information through the use of cookies, log files, text strings, browser setting and/or other tracking technology.

**Information Use**

Quepasa uses your information to provide you the features and functionality of the Service. We store information that we collect to create profiles for you and our users. Consequently, collected information is tied to your personally identifiable information to provide various offers, including offers from third parties, and improve your online experience. You voluntarily submit personally identifiable information to the Service which becomes immediately and publicly available. Any information you submit or upload, including chat room discussions, email messages, photos, videos, music, and/or blog entries, may be collected and used by others.

Quepasa also offers products and services directly and through third parties who may request financial information, including your credit card or bank account number.

From time to time, Quepasa requests information from its users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is voluntary, and you have the choice not to disclose this information.

**Information Disclosure**

Quepasa and its affiliates may share the information we collect with carefully selected nonaffiliated third-parties who provide transactional, administrative or marketing services. These parties may use your information to research, develop or offer products and services. Quepasa allows third parties to deliver online advertisements to users throughout the Service. Personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information is used to provide advertisements to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of your information by Quepasa only and does not cover the use of any technology employed by any advertisers. Please see the advertisers' various privacy policies to learn about how your information may be collected and used.

Quepasa's Service may contain links to other websites not controlled by Quepasa. Quepasa is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave Quepasa's Service, and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. 

**Opt-Out Procedures**

To opt-out of receiving commercial electronic mail messages, as defined by 15 U.S.C. Ã‚Â§ 7702, please click here [qpsupport@quepasacorp.com](mailto:qpsupport@quepasacorp.com). If you have recently opted out of receiving commercial electronic mail messages from Quepasa, we will process and honor your request as soon as administratively possible. In certain circumstances, you may continue to receive commercial electronic mail messages for products and services from other companies to whom your information was provided prior to your opt-out request.

**For Non-U.S. Users**

Quepasa is located in the United States. If you are accessing the Service from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of our Services, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

**In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy**

In the event Quepasa goes through a merger, sale, bankruptcy or other business transition, we reserve the right to transfer or assign your information we have collected as part of any business transition. In some cases, such as bankruptcy, Quepasa may not be able to control how your personal information is used.

**California Privacy Notice**

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [qpsupport@quepasacorp.com](mailto:qpsupport@quepasacorp.com) or write us at: Quepasa Corporation, Attn. Chief Executive Officer, 280 Union Square Dr., New Hope, PA 18938.
